export const chapter = "Chapter - 6: Saudi Arabia :The Land of Hot Sand  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What defines a place as a desert in terms of annual rainfall?",
        optionA: "Less than 5 inches (12.5 cm)",
        optionB: "Less than 15 inches (38 cm)",
        optionC: "Less than 10 inches (25 cm)",
        correctAnswer: "Less than 10 inches (25 cm)",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What are the three main types of deserts mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Rainforest, tundra, and steppe",
        optionB: "Hot deserts, cold deserts, and coastal deserts",
        optionC: "Savannah, taiga, and grasslands",
        correctAnswer: "Hot deserts, cold deserts, and coastal deserts",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which desert is mentioned as the largest hot desert on the planet?",
        optionA: "Gobi Desert",
        optionB: "Sahara Desert",
        optionC: "Atacama Desert",
        correctAnswer: "Sahara Desert",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the capital of Saudi Arabia?",
        optionA: "Jeddah",
        optionB: "Riyadh",
        optionC: "Mecca",
        correctAnswer: "Riyadh",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the primary natural resource mentioned for Saudi Arabia?",
        optionA: "Gold",
        optionB: "Iron ore",
        optionC: "Petroleum",
        correctAnswer: "Petroleum",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the traditional occupation of Bedouins in Saudi Arabia?",
        optionA: "Fishing",
        optionB: "Rearing cattle",
        optionC: "Farming",
        correctAnswer: "Rearing cattle",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the most dominant religion in Saudi Arabia?",
        optionA: "Christianity",
        optionB: "Buddhism",
        optionC: "Islam",
        correctAnswer: "Islam",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which type of clothing is commonly worn in Saudi Arabia to suit the climate?",
        optionA: "Heavy winter coats",
        optionB: "Traditional dress with a long cloak",
        optionC: "Swimsuits",
        correctAnswer: "Traditional dress with a long cloak",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the main industry contributing to Saudi Arabia's economic production?",
        optionA: "Textiles",
        optionB: "Petroleum products",
        optionC: "Handicrafts",
        correctAnswer: "Petroleum products",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which city is known for being the birthplace of Prophet Mohammed and a popular pilgrimage town?",
        optionA: "Jeddah",
        optionB: "Riyadh",
        optionC: "Mecca",
        correctAnswer: "Mecca",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The definition of a desert is a place that receives less than ________ of rain per year.",
        options: ["5 inches", "15 inches", "10 inches"],
        correctAnswer: "10 inches",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Hot deserts are primarily located near the Tropics, between 20° and 30° on both sides of the Equator, while cold deserts can be found in __________ regions.",
        options: ["Polar", "Temperate", "Coastal"],
        correctAnswer: "Temperate",
      },
      {
        question: "The __________ is the largest hot desert on the planet.",
        options: ["Gobi Desert", "Sahara Desert", "Atacama Desert"],
        correctAnswer: "Sahara Desert",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Saudi Arabia is situated in the Arabian Peninsula, which is the largest peninsula in the world, with the Red Sea to the ________ and the Persian Gulf to the ________.",
        options: ["North, South", "West, East", "East, West"],
        correctAnswer: "West, East",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The climate of Saudi Arabia is characterized by high temperatures and greater evaporation than precipitation, with daytime temperatures reaching as high as ________°C.",
        options: ["39°C", "49°C", "59°C"],
        correctAnswer: "49°C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Most of Saudi Arabia is a high rocky plateau covered by a vast desert, which is covered with small hills of sand called ________.",
        options: ["Oases", "Sand dunes", "Wadis"],
        correctAnswer: "Sand dunes",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Very few plants can grow in a desert climate, but in the desert regions of Saudi Arabia, you can find cacti, short shrubs, date palms, and some crops like wheat and barley grown in the ________.",
        options: ["Savannah", "Rainforest", "Oases"],
        correctAnswer: "Oases",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Owing to the harsh climate in Saudi Arabia, wildlife is limited, but you can find wolves, foxes, deer, and hyenas during the ________.",
        options: ["Winter", "Summer", "Rainy season"],
        correctAnswer: "Winter",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The traditional nomadic people of Saudi Arabia, known as Bedouins, mainly inhabit villages located near ________.",
        options: ["Coastal areas", "Mountains", "Oases"],
        correctAnswer: "Oases",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The discovery of oil has transformed Saudi Arabia into a modern country with facilities like schools, hospitals, and business centers in its urban centers, attracting a large number of migrant workers, including Indians, Pakistanis, and Sri Lankans, due to the wealth generated by ________.",
        options: ["Agriculture", "Tourism", "Petroleum"],
        correctAnswer: "Petroleum",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The Western Coastal Plains extend from Gujarat in the north to Kerala in the south.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The Malabar Coast is known for its rocky terrain.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The Konkan Coast is famous for its lagoons and backwaters.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Andaman Islands are separated from the Nicobar Islands by the Arabian Sea.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Northern Circars are the southern part of the Eastern Coastal Plains.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Lakshadweep Islands are built of volcanic deposits.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The National Emblem of India consists of three Asiatic lions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The National Anthem of India was originally composed in Bengali.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The Peacock is the National Bird of India.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Bengal Tiger was declared the National Animal of India in 1963.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
